Thank you.
谢谢
Are you okay?
你好吗
Hello. Thank you. Thank you very much.
嗨   谢谢   非常感谢
嗨   谢谢 非常感谢
He hello. Thank you. Thank you very much.
嗨   谢谢   非常感谢
He he he hello. Thank you. Thank you very much!
谢谢
How are you Indian Mi fans?
印度的米粉们你们好吗
Do you like Mi 4i?
你们喜欢小米4i吗
OK Indian Mi fans.
好的   印度米粉们
Do you like Mi band?
你们喜欢小米手环吗
We will give everyone a free Mi ban and me.
我们会给每个人一个免费小米和我
Mi fans! Do you like?
米粉们   你们喜欢吗
I'm very happy to to, to be a(n) Indian.
我很开心当一个印度人
I'm very happy to , to be a gift.
我很开心作为一个礼物
I'm a free gift. For every-everyone.
我是一个免费的礼物   对每个人
Do you like me?
你们喜欢我吗
Thank you very much!
非常感谢
Oh Indian Mi fans. Are you OK? Are you OK?
哦印度米粉们 你们好吗   你们好吗
Oh everyone, are you OK? Are you OK?
哦所有人   你们好吗   你们好吗
I I I I I I I mean are you OK? Are you OK?
我的意思是你们好吗   你们好吗
I'm very OK.
我很好